const questions = [
  { question: 'Question', answer: 'Expected Answer' },
  { question: 'Are there any beautiful buildings in Mexico City?', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: 'Are there any beaches in Mexico City?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: 'Describe your neighbourhood', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Whose wardrobe is this?', answer: 'Anna has a wardrobe' },
  { question: 'Where were you last night?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Was your grandmother Marylin Monroe?', answer: 'Positive + extra answer' },
  { question: 'Were your grandparents alive during World War II?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: 'Where did you buy your watch?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Did you bring the cake for the party?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: 'What did you do last Summer?', answer: '3 irregular verbs' },
  { question: 'Do you love swimming?', answer: 'Negative + extra answer' },
  { question: 'Can you cook?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: 'Could you run 42km in 2012?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: 'What can you do?', answer: '3 verbs' },
  { question: 'Do you have to do much exercise in order to get fit?', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: 'What do you have to do when you go school?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'What are you doing?', answer: 'Open, 3 verbs' },
  { question: 'What do you do?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Are you reading a book?', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: 'I usually ____ by car', answer: 'travel / travelling' },
  { question: 'Are you wearing a dress?', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: 'Use 3 comparative adjectives in 3 sentences', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Use 3 superlative adjectives in 3 sentences', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Have you ever been to London?', answer: 'Positive + where did you go?' },
  { question: 'Has Erika been to the gym this week?', answer: 'Negative' },
  { question: '3 sentences using present perfect', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: '3 sentences using past simple', answer: 'Irregular verbs' },
  { question: 'What are your PLANS for next year?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'What are you going to do next year?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Are you going to travel the world next year?', answer: 'Positive' },
  { question: 'What should you do when you go on vacation?', answer: 'Open' },
  { question: 'Should I take a sweater to Mexico City?', answer: 'Negative' }
];

export default questions;